(Han Seok-kyu)
(Pei Xiancheng)
(Li Rui)
(President Shin Project)
(This drama is purely fictional
Appearing characters, place names, institutions)
(Events, groups, occupations, etc. are related to
It has nothing to do with reality (I hereby inform you)
(Child actors are all accompanied by their guardians
Photographed in a safe environment)
(Episode 4)
With...
There are...
Almost hit
Okay, got it
About to hit
Medium...abominable
They have already invested 10,000 yuan
At least let me win one
Why can't I catch even one?
I've caught more than ten of them.
How many? Ten
You? Why?
Of course it's because I'm awesome
Uncle, I mean
Why can you catch so many
You want me to teach you...
Is there a way to clip a doll?
Yeah, teach me
What do you want to give me, uncle?
Clamp it first and then talk about it
This is called negotiation
Negotiate?
what is negotiation
it's you and me
exchange what each other wants
Ah...
Invest money
Hey, if you didn’t catch it
You have to pay me back
good
Very good
Come on, take a look
Take a good look, eh
First, choose the doll you want
That one I want the yellow chick
Uncle, don’t choose a doll that’s too heavy.
why
Because your skills are not good enough and you can’t clip them.
Got it
Quick clip
The clip has three claws, right?
Well, grab the neck from the left and right sides with both hands
Then pinch the remaining claws from the middle of the doll's head
Yeah
For dolls with big heads, just clip the head...
Hit, caught...
You are awesome. High five.
Hello
hey what are you doing
I want a box of ghost saliva
I negotiated with you first
Now it's uncle's turn
Got it. Let's go to the stationery store.
Take it, little devil, your devilish saliva
come on give it to you
Right
this is negotiation
Negotiation completed
OK
Go back
Oh uncle
Huh?
Next time if I spend 5,000 yuan, I still can’t get it
Then give up
It’s not a good idea to spend 10,000 yuan on clip-on dolls, right?
Hello
You salivate over the 2,000 yuan
Just teach me the skills of clamping dolls
I earned it
Those are teaching online?
I also taught my father
But he still can't even catch half of it.
Because his skills are not as good as mine
Goodbye uncle
Oops
(President Shin Project)
Alas, I forgot to take the book
Didn't you say that before?
When negotiating, rather than treating the other party as an enemy
It will be more valuable to use the other party
Is it the same this time?
Li Xiangxian and his mother
They were all captured on the CCTV at the exit entrance.
you are not using me
Turn off all network base stations
Help him secure an escape route?
When you moved Li Xiangxian away
Deceive all police officers and civil servants
hiding prisoners
Instigating escape
A term apprenticeship of less than three years
Penalty or fine of 5 million yuan
I always thought you and I were in the same camp
Come out quickly
It will be very busy if you ride a motorcycle.
Hello
Hurry up and ride
Didn’t I tell you that turning is just like going straight?
Relax your forearms
Look at you
The trapezius muscles are working too hard
Don't hold it too tightly, be gentle
Relax and soften your hands
I feel like both my grandma and grandma can ride better than you.
How did you get your car's driver's license?
It's all your fault for nagging me, which makes me even more confused.
You dare to talk about me
When you were just writing the topic, weren't you also nagging me all the time?
How can you talk to the teacher in this tone?
I'm the teacher now, okay?
Don't talk anymore. Just go ride a circle and come back by yourself.
uncle
Oh, Yeyeon, don’t run.
Yeyan, uncle picked up this doll and wants to give it to you
Did you really catch it, uncle?
Of course
How many times have you clamped it?
Once? Five times?
Or ten times? It doesn’t matter how many times you pinch it
Clamping is the key point
You'll earn money if you catch it in one go
Otherwise it's a waste of money
How does your tone match?
Sister Shi On is exactly the same
My sister said so
So she never let me pick up dolls
Ye Yan
You have to keep it a secret from Sister Shi On
这只是我花了一堆钱才夹到的
What I said, uncle
You want me to keep this secret from my sister?
Yeah
So what should I name it?
Name?
You didn't say a word while they were being stitched.
Why is there so much fuss about removing the stitches now?
Not here, but feet
Oops
Say it earlier
Didn't you say this was an injury sustained while working?
Didn't the boss pay for the medical expenses?
Forget it
How embarrassing
(Later entering the business district)
Li Xiangxian and his mother
They were all captured on the CCTV at the exit entrance.
Did it do anything wrong?
What?
What did that station do wrong?
Otherwise why did you take it?
Rags tortured him severely
It's okay
I've only been working for a short time
Are you getting burnt out soon?
No, that's because, president, you treated me...
concealed the facts
what did i do to you
And secretly breaking the law, right?
What's wrong with me
It's okay
It's just job burnout.
Hello, we are not open yet
Hey, he is not a guest
What's wrong
It seems that business has been good recently. We even hired employees.
He's not an employee, he's an airborne trooper
Give way
What? Get out of the way
I'm working
Why should I leave my kitchen?
Technically this is my kitchen, right?
I didn't take any deposit from you
Since you want to be so domineering
Then why don't you even charge rent from me?
Do you change your oil every day?
Don’t you know after watching it?
Of course I know
Where did you know
By the way...
Where is the glutinous rice flour?
Why are you looking for glutinous rice flour there?
The glutinous rice flour is here
(glutinous rice flour)
I was just planning to go out and buy glutinous rice flour.
airborne troops
You happen to be going out to buy this, right?
What?
Glutinous rice flour
yes...yes
You are too sloppy in your business, right?
Who are you talking about?  Me?
I am very dedicated to doing business.
Hello airborne troops
Please be fair
What to say?
Careful
Right that...
Our fried chicken restaurant is really...
Very delicious
Hello
glutinous rice flour
I'm out
Go quickly and come back quickly
Oops, this employee is not very good.
Not employees, but airborne troops
He will resign soon
I won't choose such a rigid person.
He's not very good at lying. I'm very satisfied.
Just the talent you need
Oops
You old-fashioned people
He always pops into other people's stores suddenly like this
Has Judge Kim been here too?
Otherwise, who do you think is responsible?
That kind of guy put him in?
Oops, it's a step too late
I should put my people in
Am I a target?
What is the arrangement or not?
This damn fried chicken restaurant
I seem to have seen that person somewhere
(Park Myung Jin)
Right
(Affiliated to: Tianren Food)
Hundreds, thousands, hundreds, thousands, millions...
(Related information: Tianren Food)
27 trillion?
Why do business owners come to our fried chicken restaurant?
Who is the president?
President Shin?
He's not kidding
President Shin has a really wide network of contacts
He is our government
The negotiators we hired with great difficulty
What about such a powerful person?
Maybe I can’t find any information?
Is there any secret to the fried chicken restaurant?
If you want to know something
Just go and find out for yourself
(I'm so happy to have you)
What's wrong?
That person is the owner, right?
Are you here for the shopping mall reconstruction?
Well, that's right
But where are you going dressed up like this?
I'm going to visit the graves of my ancestors
What did the shopkeeper say?
Do you want to continue running this fried chicken restaurant?
how do i know
Where are you?
That incident recently caused me tossing and turning.
Afraid of becoming a forgotten old man
What's wrong?
are you retiring
I'm still in good health. What about retirement?
I don't even need to wear reading glasses to thread a needle.
That being the case
Just keep doing it. Is there any problem?
The problem lies here
Our owner, President Jin said
There is no laundry room in the newly built shopping mall
What?
Who decided that?
how do i know
During this period of time, in order to please President Jin, I
Not only did he iron his shirt for free,
He also took good care of his wife's mink coat.
As a result, he stabbed me in the back
So are you going to ask your ancestors for help?
No
I have something else to report to my ancestors today
I want to reopen with it
I feel like saying hello to my ancestors
Brother, you are already that old
Why are you talking about starting over?
Anyway, that's right
No
Can't open yet
This is very important
I'm back
hello
Well hello
What does Pluto say?
Has he met President Kim?
President Zhang said that the owner...
Forget it
I don't want to know at all I'm leaving
Brother, let’s have a cup of coffee before we go.
He's obviously super curious
Hello airborne troops
let's go have lunch
It's only 11 o'clock now
Hey come to Pluto
Add an additional portion of Nanjian Meatballs
OK Nanjian Meatballs Shi Wen
have you had lunch
Not yet
Are you going to deliver food?
Yes
Thank you for your hard work
Have a nice meal
Okay, be careful on the road
My sister had stitches on her arm
There are bruises on the belly too
But how did my sister get injured?
She said she fell while riding a motorcycle
Lie
Liar?
The motorcycle is totally fine
I don’t know who hurt my sister
Uncle, help me find that person and teach him a lesson
Good
Uncle will definitely find him
Then teach him a lesson
Let's eat this first. This is for hospitality.
Thank you, President Zhang
Are there any troublesome guests here?
Because this guy pretends to be pretentious on a live broadcast
Shi Wen was forced to send him out
I was scolded to death when I sold it.
How could I be pretending?
It was you who asked me to deliver food
It just happened to be photographed
Hello
I asked you to deliver food
I didn’t ask you to appear on the show
Just because you look cool in a suit over there
That’s why Shi Wen was scolded.
Stop talking
A guy called me a few days ago
He said something about the food being soaked and started cursing.
When I look at the order
He ordered fried rice and sweet and sour pork
I obviously put fried rice
Fried sauce and sweet and sour sauce are packaged separately
So I asked him what soaked it
He actually said the delivery boy was rude
It makes the food taste bad
What the hell are you talking about?
How was it handled later?
Oops, he keeps saying that he needs to file a complaint.
As a result, we ordered food from us again today.
Is that the place where we just went to deliver food?
(Elevator under maintenance)
(Elevator failure under repair)
Longba this bastard
But I will still send it up
Bastard
you are late
I heard the elevator was out of order
Did you come up the stairs?
He was a lawyer before working with me
Are you really a lawyer?
Yes
Then why do you want to work at a fried chicken restaurant?
The situation is a bit complicated...
President Zhang
What you said sounds weird
What happened to the fried chicken restaurant?
Did I say how about a fried chicken restaurant?
I just feel like the lawyer is here
Working in a fried chicken restaurant is weird
wait a moment
Hello this is Pluto
What?
The noodles are all stuck together and can't be removed at all
The sweet and sour pork was also soggy and rotten.
How do you want me to eat it?
Your delivery boy?
I asked her to take it back and do it again, but she just refused.
How exactly do you train your employees?
Hello
Listen to the phone
Just refund the money
OK
Really speechless
Almost starved to death
As a result, this kind of damn thing was sent to me
And you said you want a refund?
Hello
It’s not enough to ask you to compensate me.
Even if I haven’t read any books
This is also basic common sense, right?
You have such a high degree of education
How could you do such a ridiculous thing?
I know the elevator is broken
And you torture people on purpose, right?
I will refund your money
Go order takeout from other stores
I won't charge you for the sauce.
Otherwise, just eat the stir-fried noodles with rice and sauce.
Where should I go to clean up the garbage?
You loser...
Is it still hurting?
So why run away and get yourself hurt?
Meeting a classmate after a long absence
I originally wanted to chat with you
It was you who knocked it over. You have to clear it up yourself.
It's best if you sort the garbage for me properly.
really disgusting
Just a delivery boy, are you crazy?
Li Shiwen
Abominable
Damn it, you're dead
Li Shiwen
If the guest has a contemptuous attitude
With garbage, scum, etc.
Insulting words to the delivery clerk
Suspected of violating section 1 of the Criminal Code
Article 311 Crime of public insult
Can be sentenced to fixed-term imprisonment of not more than one year or criminal detention
or a fine of not more than two million yuan
In short
If that unreasonable
What did the guest do to Shi On?
Please contact me immediately
good
This matter must be kept secret from Shi Wen
I will also do my best to help
thank you
Brother, I really shouldn’t have to submit to this.
if it weren't for that
You have already become famous...
I told you I like it here
Interpols are responsible for catching criminals.
Moreover, if you really become famous
It also depends on the faces of those senior officials.
Pulling innocent juniors into the water
That kind of day doesn't suit me
That's right
I'm just a team leader, what can I do?
The people above have been putting pressure on
The subordinates complained again and again
I'm going to trouble you later
This is what I want to say
Don't feel uncomfortable just because I'm older
Just like with other team members, just be casual.
Don't worry, we won't be particularly lenient to our seniors
Let's go to a dinner party when they arrive.
As for work handover...
Just take your time
Thank you
(North Gyeonggi Police Station)
(Autopsy report)
(Police officer in charge
Gyeonggi Northern Police Station Criminal Mobile Team Choi Cheol)
(2009 Sihe 4116
Li Hanzhun traffic accident)
(National Institute of Scientific Research)
(Yoon Dong-hee is the one setting up the trap?)
airborne troops
can you act
What?
Forget it
I saw just now that you are not very good at observing words and expressions.
It would be terrible if I got screwed by you
What else is he planning?
I can do it
Why do you just say you can do it all day long?
I'll prove it to you
What do you need me to do?
(New oil with fresh chicken! Fried Chicken Headquarters)
Schwinn
You have been airborne these days
Let's go deliver food together with the troops.
What? Why
Let him know the route
Learn how to deliver food by the way
I don't want
We are so busy, he will only hinder me
I don't want to either, okay?
And what skills are needed to deliver food?
Just give it to the guests, right?
you are really disgusting
airborne troops
Have you ever played with dolls?
You don’t have to know the method to get it right.
It seems simple, but actually it requires skills.
Brat, you deliver food too
Delivering food is also difficult
Schwinn, am I right?
Forget it
Just let him live like this for the rest of his life.
Didn’t I say you could act?
Is that okay? It’s okay.
Follow me out quickly
I really can't stand you
Hurry up
What are you doing?
What else can I do? Go deliver food?
Or should I ride?
Let's go
"Off path"
Where are you riding to?
Not this way
What you ride is different from the navigation
We were about to turn left there just now.
"Off path"
(Five minutes remaining)
It was shortened by five minutes
See it?
This is the trick to delivering food
Let's go. You don't need a navigation anyway.
we set off
Be careful on the road
Why do you think these two are a perfect match?
No, it's a pity that Shi On matched him.
mother child
Don't cry
Looking at uncle and mother
Uncle will save you
It's okay. Nothing is okay.
I...
I'm not crazy
It's suspicious even if the CCTV is turned off.
I told you Han Zhiying
and Li Hanzhun did not die in an accident
This is a murder case
You don’t know Yoon Dong Hee
Is this guy deliberately taking pills to pretend to be crazy?
(New oil with fresh chicken! Fried Chicken Headquarters)
welcome
Are you alone?
Yes
Choose a place to sit
Come on, what do you want?
I want original fried chicken and Coke
Good
Arriving seven minutes faster than the navigation
She's really skilled
A total of 20,000 yuan
I'll go in and get my wallet. Come in and wait at the entrance.
I'll just wait outside
whatever you want
Why is it you again?
That's why I have to ask, what kind of delivery person are you?
From early morning to evening this morning
I've ordered takeout five or six times
madman
Give me the money for the fried chicken.
before that
You made a mess in the hallway of our apartment
You should have to pay a cleaning fee, right?
It's your own fault
Why should I pay the cleaning fee?
You crazy woman, how dare you go even further?
You look exactly like you did in high school
Have you grown older in vain?
She is just a woman who is too poor to graduate
I cheered you up because you were pitiful. What else do you want?
The cleaning fee should be offset with the compensation.
Are you serious?
what are you doing
Li Shiwen, are you okay?
Who are you?
Abominable
Let's go
I'm really fine
Wait
Do you have the means to ride a bike? Let me ride.
I just said I'm fine
I'm usually weak
What happened just now?
When did I lose my strength?
I'm from the police academy
Taekwondo Level 3 Kendo Level 2...
Pretending again
Right
fried chicken money
That bedbug bastard, really.
Has he been bullying you since high school?
What to look at
Hey, from now on it's up to you to run errands and buy cigarettes.
i have no money
what
This guy...
Be obedient
I told you to be obedient
Hey, bow your head
Shouldn't you...
I didn't drop out of school because of him
You go back first
I'll take a taxi back
Are you going to go up to them again?
Choi Yong-pal is a complete gangster and lunatic
Being involved with him will give you a headache
Don't fight him
It's okay
He will have more headaches if he has anything to do with me.
don't worry
I won't do dangerous things
I took the fried chicken money and went back
Then I'll leave first
You have to come back soon
good
Be careful on the road
Come back soon
Come...
Please use it slowly
Guest, do you live near here?
No
Is this your first time visiting our store?
yes
It's okay
If you need anything, tell me anytime.
uncle
Oops, no need
Shi-on delivers takeaways
How do you come back on your own? Where are the airborne troops?
Choi Yong-pal is a complete gangster and lunatic
Being involved with him will give you a headache
Don't fight him
Forget it
No. Why doesn't he answer the phone?
where are you going
I'll go take a look
No, don't go
Hello Schwinn
Schwinn
Guest Sorry
Because I have something urgent
Must close now
Can you help me install the rest?
OK thank you
(Uncle)
uncle
Where are you now Schwinn?
I'm following a suspicious car
You don't have to do anything until I'm gone
Do you know
Got it, so come here quickly
(Schwin)
Hello
There's someone inside
Is no one here?
Schwinn
Where is the car?
Where is the car now?
The phone was connected but no one answered
That's right
Shi Wen, go over there and take a look.
good
There's someone inside
Cao Bili
airborne troops
Must be established
(fall)
airborne troops
Answer
Cao Bili
There's someone inside
airborne troops
Cao Bili
President
where
Uncle, where are the airborne troops?
No
airborne troops
Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up.
Go up quickly
Hurry up Hurry up
What are you doing, telling you to go up quickly?
Come up quickly
airborne troops
Pull him out quickly, okay
Alab caught it
Take your time. Are you ready?
two three
take your time
Help me cut this open. Okay
What's going on? Really?
Airborne, are you okay?
Can you stand up?
Well...
I'm fine, but can you hold me back a little?
Good
let me come
Schwinn
You call an ambulance first and take him to the hospital.
Good
You two, talk to me first.
where is your office
please follow me
Go quickly
are you okay
Are you feeling uncomfortable anywhere?
There's a big swelling on my head
Maybe he was knocked unconscious by something
wait a moment
Although my driving skills are not very good
But I know quite a lot about cars.
There is a device in the trunk that can be opened
can't stand you
Why do you treat one like this?
A man who just nearly died
Do you really want to die?
Didn't I say that guy Long Ba is a lunatic?
Don't provoke him. Why did you go there?
Do you know how cruel that guy is?
Sorry for making you worry
You should find another job in the future.
Not qualified to be a delivery boy
where are you going
Let's go together
good or not
No
I'm just afraid that you'll worry
I just wanted to make it easier for everyone.
all because of me
Because I almost killed you
Sorry, I shouldn't have been joking
thank you for worrying about me
(24 hours CCTV recording)
Strange why it wasn’t recorded
What do you mean by this?
What does not record mean?
Is this sticker for fun?
I only discovered it now
Alab
Did you turn off the CCTV?
No, it's not me
So was it normal before?
What about other employees?
Everyone just got off work and went to have a dinner together.
Then why are you two here?
In order to count the quantity to be sent to the iron factory tomorrow
So Alab and I came back after dinner
Do you often have dinner together?
Get together once in a while
The boss made a reservation at the barbecue restaurant today
Let our employees eat by themselves
Is it just employees?
Yes
The boss is really nice
This is really good
Hey
Oh
What's going on
I didn't call you first
Master Jin, help me find someone.
Who?  Which person?
The faster, the better. The more data, the better.
Yeah
what did the doctor say
The doctor said it was fine and there was no concussion.
The swollen area will disappear in a few days.
I just said it's okay
Why do you have to come for CT scan?
You are so good. I was hit on the back of the head until I fainted.
Even being put into a car press in a scrapyard was fine.
Really lucky
No evidence or diagnosis
What can we do to deal with them?
It's all my fault
How could it be you who caused it?
The bad guy is Long Ba
Do you want to call the police first?
Didn't I just say that there is no evidence?
I will find a way to solve this matter
as president
This can never be calculated like this
How bold you dare to touch my employees
i will do it my way
handle this matter personally
What about me?
Just have a good rest
Then I have to find the evidence in my own way
There is no CCTV in our apartment.
Isn't that closed-circuit television?
That's just for show
Liar
(Multi-function CCTV recording)
(Crime Prevention CCTV recording)
Can I have access to this CCTV?
I was attacked around here
but no evidence
Let me confirm it for you
CCTV of this number
Patrolman, please give him the application form.
Wow
There is a lot of information in this room that can be checked
Still a little short of it. Everything else has been found.
Why is it so different?
It's lunch break time now
You don’t know that civil servants must
Do I need to eat during lunch break?
I know
When my life was almost in danger
Didn’t you also go to eat within the stipulated time?
Don't say irrelevant things
I'm going to close the line
Send it to me quickly
(Fried Chicken Headquarters)
(Closed today)
Will things go well if we handle things the way the president did?
Airborne troops, what about you?
I'm also dealing with it very seriously
When I was still working in a law firm
I am almost always responsible for contacting people.
Is this so?
But how did you know, President?
know what
Choi Yong-min wants to attack Shi On
how could i know
I don’t even know who Choi Yong-min is
That's not right
Wasn’t the president just called
Am I secretly Shi Wen's bodyguard?
所以我才会跟着她去送外卖
The president’s mobile phone is still down
Installed a location tracking app
That's because Pluto Zhang
The boss said there was a troublesome customer
Just prepared as a precaution
Fortunately, Shi Wen was protected by doing this.
I also saved your life.
It's just that you prepare in advance and you can kill two birds with one stone.
To put it simply, you have earned it
Have a good rest
Where are you going?  Do you need to go together?
No, today is a day off.
Airborne troops, just have a good rest.
I'll be back soon
(Fried Chicken Headquarters)
Who? Your takeaway has arrived?
I didn't order takeout
The takeaway has arrived
I just said I didn’t order takeout.
Isn't this number 1203?
Which guy orders takeout to someone else's house?
Look at your lack of standards
Longba should be you, right?
Who is the uncle?
Police?
Hello
It's because of people like you
Impurities only appear in iron recycling
South Korea's steel industry suffered huge losses
bed bugs
You hit my employee and stuffed him in the trunk of your car.
Are you still planning to scrap the car?
What are you talking about? Where can I be?
do you have evidence
Evidence?
Evidence...
Right here you bastard
Hello
Yeah, I've recorded his voice and I'll pass it on to you.
(New message added)
(Audio generation completed)
Long time no see, President Shin
A while ago...
thank you
The person I think of in a hurry
only you
you did a good job
I feel very grateful to be able to help.
Ji Woo must have grown up a lot, right?
How is she doing?
She is already a college student
I went to see her last month
She's doing very well
That's it
By the way, Mrs. Zhu
Ji Woo’s previous photos
Are you wearing a white dress?
The kind you take with a doll
Is this this one?
Sir, sorry
I have something urgent at the moment
Yesterday I saw a man holding this photo
Where did you see it? What does he look like?
He has been to our store
Jin Yongyu
Jin Yongyu was at that time...
Yes
It's that bastard
Ji Woo's dad
You can't concentrate at all today
I just think...
Why take the diploma exam?
Then why did you want to take the exam in the first place?
I don’t want to be looked down upon by people like Long Ba
But what if you passed the diploma exam?
Even you, a first-year police officer, almost died.
That's why we have to make him pay the price even more.
Longba...
Have you been bullying you all this time?
Probably...
A month ago
I met him by chance when I was delivering food
He's obviously still a bastard himself
But they gossip about whether I have graduated or not.
After hearing this, I felt my pride was hurt.
super angry
No matter what the motive is
Just do it
Even so, what can it change?
After passing the diploma examination
Me too...
It's me the same
Still nothing and no power
It will only cause you trouble in vain
And Long Ba’s father is running for election again this time.
you are powerful
are you stupid
I know you are just because
I helped me with tutoring out of pity
you are really powerful
you see
This is the preamble to the Constitution of the Republic of Korea
That is to standardize the governance structure of the Republic of Korea.
and the supreme law on the rights and obligations of citizens
No law can violate the constitution
And...
In simple terms
This is the most powerful law in Korea
What was the first thing I wrote about?
Article 1 Item 1
The Republic of Korea is a democratic republic
Item 2
The sovereignty of the Republic of Korea belongs to its citizens
All power comes from the people
Didn’t you say that Long Ba’s father is a city councilor?
That person’s strength also comes from the people
That's just the content in social textbooks, right?
So
Do you have the right to vote?
that's your power
For Long Ba’s father
your vote is very important
Local elections are coming soon
(The Republic of Korea is a democratic republic)
(The sovereignty of the Republic of Korea belongs to its citizens
All power comes from the people)
Stop delivering food and become a judge.
That's more suitable for you
Is this a compliment?
Idiot
Praise me in memory of you
Let me treat you to dinner
You can go back after eating
(President Shin)
Didn't you say you have a holiday?
Didn’t you tell me to have a rest today?
Didn't you take a full day's rest?
So what? I haven’t even had dinner yet.
are you hungry
Do you want fried chicken for you?
Why did you call me here?
I want to share information about Longba with you
Of course I'll still handle it my way
sit down
Just like after saving Li Xiangxian
Is it the same as secretly sending him abroad?
President
You know that's where prisoners are hidden, right?
Thanks to Li Xiangxian, corruption can be exposed
Also redress for those cancer patients who died unjustly
I know but...
Hey, do you want to watch him die?
Make that poor mother lose two children
No matter how sad the rest of her life will be?
If it were you, what would you do?
Hey
Chief Executive Officer Kim
what to do what happened
Assistant, how are you doing?
What are you doing? Am I handsome?
I know. Can you come over earlier?
Master Jin, have you found out everything?
Of course there is
Hey, give me a cup of coffee
I'll go rush
No, it's okay
This guy is very naughty
I'll make it. Just boil the water.
But...
What did you ask about?
Cui Xiongzhi
(Briefing by Representative Choi Woong-sik)
Three-term city councilor
(Choi Woong-sik)
Including Fuheng Parking Lot
That area is all Choi Woong-sik’s land.
The parking lot was rented by Chae Eui-soo
Monthly rent is very cheap
Chae Eui-soo? What is the relationship between the two of them?
The relationship between brothers and sisters
Their sons are also friends
Choi Woong-sik... Choi Woong-sik...
(Cui Xiongsik will also accompany you all the way)
During the election he was also involved in the campaign team
Also serves as president of the support club
(City Councilor Choi Woong-sik)
Just hearing you say it makes me feel like something is fishy
It seems there is a lot of oil and water to be fished out of it.
However, Choi Woong-sik’s power in Mageon City
Bigger than the mayor
But why is he elected as a city councilor?
I feel like electing a member of Congress
Or the head of the local government can also
It’s not that he’s afraid of not being able to choose, it’s just that he doesn’t want to choose.
Because he has no shortage of money or power
His son is an asshole
(Choi Yong-min and Chae Seung-hyuk)
Starting from junior high school, I beat my classmates and ostracized them.
Do all the bad things
But not a single word was reported in the news
Because his father's power is above the law
This is so outrageous
Covering up school bullying
What about the victims?
You know about school bullying
How long will the psychological trauma last?
Why are you angry with me?
Hello airborne troops
Are you like this because of Shi On?
Yes
Partly because of Schwinn
Also because of other victims
Choi Yong-min’s father Choi Woong-sik
Will you run for election this time too?
He already held a campaign meeting last week
It’s about to be chosen for the fourth time
How is this possible? Who allowed him to choose?
Calm down...
Hey, you two, be careful.
I heard that you were almost crushed to death under a pile of scrap metal.
People who treat human life as a joke
More than expected
don't worry
I won't die
airborne troops
Do you know what my nickname is in the Middle East?
Never Die
What about in the United States?
golden master
Did you tell him about me?
No there isn't...
Die Hard
Stop laughing
What are you laughing at? Do you understand?
No, I like watching movies very much
My mom is a Booth Willis fan
Hey, don't mention Brother Booth.
He has retired
Where is this dear friend?
Even if you want to die, you can't die
Right?
(Ma Xian’s opportunity to take off!
No. 1 Choi Woong-sik City Councilor’s Office)
(Uicheng Building)
(City Councilor Choi Woong-sik)
Hurry up and make tea for the guests
Yes
For you Yes
(Contribution Award)
Please drink tea. Okay
I'm very familiar with that underdeveloped business district.
I was born and raised in that area for forty years
So that's it
That’s why the citizens are like this
I have been asking you, Congressman, to pay you a visit.
Heck, even without a member’s badge
Neighbors should also help each other
Yes
But sir you
Did something sad happen?
Actually, what about me...
He makes a living by doing takeout business
I have really met all kinds of customers
But this guest is really too domineering.
Are there still such stupid people today?
Yes, it really does exist
MP
Our delivery boy is being bullied so badly
I asked him to try to record it if he could.
Could you please listen to it for me? Okay...
It's your own fault
Why should I pay the cleaning fee?
How dare you go even further?
Have you changed a lot?
How dare you talk back to me
She is just a woman who is too poor to graduate
Hey, wake up. It's daytime now.
So what? I'm leaving Korea today.
Now that woman has no bodyguards.
Hey, are you crazy?
Li Shiwen, that delivery girl
Do you want to let her take the lead?
Homeless man with a motorcycle
Only then will she wake up?
Oh, stop it now. Hey
I cheered you up because you were pitiful. What else do you want?
The cleaning fee should be offset with the compensation.
It's my son
It turns out you came here after knowing everything.
sorry
I will try my best to do what I can do for you
I'm not that indifferent to right from wrong.
Those who are responsible must take responsibility, right?
Is this guy definitely dead?
Hey don't worry
My dad will help me sort it out.
So who should be responsible for this?
Is it your son or you?
That guy...
Not dead?
Oh my God, that's Schwinn's motorcycle.
Schwinn
Just say it directly
ok
Now you come here and threaten me like this...
How do you say threat?
I'm not the type to take it
A person who threatens others with his wife's problems
I'm here to negotiate with you, Representative Choi Woong-sik.
As long as this election
You cancel your candidate registration and withdraw from the candidacy
I will save you
He was violent towards Shi Wen and planned to kill Pili.
and you coerce the victim.
Planning to hide the truth
If you can withdraw from the election, take full responsibility
I will save you
How about you want to negotiate with me?
Still...
I really want to be...
Threatening to take a look?
(Contribution Award)
(Maxian City Citizen Supervision Group Federation)
(President Shin Project)
This can't be used as evidence in court, right?
Other evidence is needed
How can I have time to slowly defeat those bad guys?
I am candidate No. 9 Shin Jae-yi
Will definitely promote this policy
If we unite and pool our strength
Catch them all
It seems that there is only one way after all.
Don't look at me like this. I'm also good at fighting.
Must persist to the end
election